Anna Phillips

t: 321.745.0268 e: annaphillipsse@gmail.com Orlando, FL <u>Portfolio</u> <u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Skills

React.js, Redux, JavaScript, Python, Flask, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, postgreSQL, Node.js, Express, Git, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Indesign, Render

Projects

Inkling live site github

JavaScript · Python · React / Redux · Flask · PostgreSQL · HTML5 · CSS3

A note-taking app with rich text editing, print, dark-mode.

- Used Quill Rich Text Editor to implement saving notes in highly customizable format
- Implemented CSS techniques to enable site-wide light and dark mode switching functionality.
- Leveraged the power of useEffect and event handling to successfully implement an autosave feature.

Recollecting Dairy live site | github

JavaScript · Python · React / Redux · Flask · PostgreSQL · HTML5 · CSS3

Recreates the popular to-do list app, Remember the Milk.

- Developed a parsing function to extract tag characters from a single input field for populating backend forms.
- Utilized dynamic rendering techniques to display and present content efficiently.

AirBnB Clone <u>live site</u> <u>aithub</u>

JavaScript · React.js · Redux.js · Express.js · Sequelize.js · HTML5 · CSS3

Mimics the experience of renting out properties and finding places to stay.

- Implemented efficient code execution and reduced redundancy by employing helper functions.
- Mastered state management techniques and adeptly integrated frontend and backend functionalities for seamless operation.

Education

App Academy | July 2022 - July 2023 | Online Course

Immersive software development course with focus on full stack web development

University of Central Florida | August 2013 - August 2016 | Orlando, FL

Graphic Design, Degree not completed

- Began as a Computer Science major
- Courses include Intro to Computer Science and Web Design

Brevard Community College | August 2011 - May 2013 | Cocoa, FL

AA Degree

Experience

Stock Coordinator | December 2022 - Present

Merchandise Stocker | July 2019 - December 2022

Team Captain | May 2018 - July 2019

Merchandise Sales Associate | July 2013 - May 2018

Universal Orlando Resort

- Supervised the operation of 4 merchandise venues
- Submit orders to maintain stock and minimize damaging products
- Collaborated with other departments to oversee annual inventory
- Trained over 30 new team members on company policies, procedures, and culture.